<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ruicosta.io</title><link>https://ruicosta.io/</link><description>Recent content on ruicosta.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright/><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 19:53:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ruicosta.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ruicosta.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ruicosta.io/about/</guid><description>You’ve guessed the name from the website link.
Most of my day is spent around technology.
I’ve dedicated most of my career to building a platform that enables the Internet of Moving Things. Our goal is to enable devices, for now mostly vehicles, to connect to each other and the Internet. This mesh network allows us to have more resilient wireless Internet access to the services surrounding us and enable new ways to live our lives.</description></item><item><title>Other</title><link>https://ruicosta.io/other/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ruicosta.io/other/</guid><description>Not the Rui Costa you are looking for? Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of other Rui Costas out there, I&amp;rsquo;ve met throughout the years:
Rui Costa | Keywords: soccer Rui Costa | Keywords: cycling Rui Costa | Keywords: Codavel, Streambolico, network coding Rui Costa | Keywords: Ubiwhere Known more Rui Costas out there? Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>5 lessons about effective communication and personal growth</title><link>https://ruicosta.io/posts/2017/02/5-lessons-about-effective-communication-and-personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 19:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ruicosta.io/posts/2017/02/5-lessons-about-effective-communication-and-personal-growth/</guid><description>2016 was quite an intense year.
Highlights — non-exhaustive
A series of Portuguese endeavors out in the stars (Euro cup, UN leadership, Portugal as a startup nation); A thousand-year-old broken-unity taking new steps; A joyful environmental and safety positive impact by the increasing rollout electrically powered and assisted-driving vehicles. Lowlights — even less exhaustive
The increasing number of refugees; The almost cartoonish U.S. election result; The series of music stars leaving us ahead of time.</description></item></channel></rss>